Guide to the Dept. of Food Science records, 1900-2002.
Department of Food Science records
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Dept. of Food Science records, 1900-2002.
21-26-3893
New York State College of Agriculture. Department of Food Science.
1.4 cubic feet., 44.4 MB
Photographs, printed materials, research materials.
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Glass negatives of dairy barns, cheesemaking, and dairy science.
COLLECTION DESCRIPTION
Glass negatives of dairy barns, cheesemaking, and dairy science.
Includes "Food Science Facts" (1981-1984), Food Science Club files, including its newsletter (1974-1993), booklets listing Food Science Graduates (1990-1995) and other information pertaining to the Institute of Food Science.
Also faculty meeting minutes (1986-1990); Dept. Research Projects (1986, 1988), dept. brochures and other department files from the 1980s and a video "A Matter of Judgement: The Case for Food Safety in the Supermarket Deli."
SUBJECTS
Names:
New York State College of Agriculture.; New York State College of Agriculture. Department of Food Science.
Subjects:
Food industry and trade. -- Education (Higher); Dairying -- New York (State); Dairy science.; Cheesemaking.; Dairy barns.; Cheesemaking; Dairy barns
Form and Genre Terms:
Negatives.
INFORMATION FOR USERS
CONTAINER LIST
- Glass Slides of Dairy Barns, Cheesemaking and Dairy Science (Box 1)
- Glass Slides of Diary Barns, Cheesemaking and Dairy Science (Box 2)
- Booklets listing the Graduates of Food Science, 1990-1995 (Box 3, Folder 1)
- Food Science Club Newsletter, 1974-1993 (Box 3, Folder 2)
- "Food Science Facts" - The Institute of Food Science and Food Science Extension Publication, 1981-09-1982-12 (Box 3, Folder 3)
- "Food Science Facts" - The Institute of Food Science and Food Science Extension Publication, 1983-01-1984-05; 1987-05 (Box 3, Folder 4)
- Food Science Club Minutes and Memos, 1978-1994 (Box 3, Folder 5)
- Message from Department Chair, 1980-1988 (Box 3, Folder 6)
- Department Brochures, 1970; 1980-1989 (Box 3, Folder 7)
- Gum and Starch Technology - 18th Annual Symposium, 1983-11 (Box 3, Folder 8)
- Faculty Meeting Minutes, 1986-1987 (Box 3, Folder 9)
- Faculty Meeting Minutes, 1988-1990 (Box 3, Folder 10)
- Department Research Projects, 1986 (Box 3, Folder 11)
- Department Research Projects, 1988 (Box 3, Folder 12)
- Graduate Field of Food Science and Technology - Lists of Faculty and Guide Book, 1988; 1990-1999 (Box 3, Folder 13)
- Food Science Laboratory Dedication Brochure, 1988-11 (Box 3, Folder 14)
- "Food Science At Cornell: A Century of Excellence 1902-2002" by David Bandler and Robert Holland, 2002 (Box 3, Folder 15)
- Food Science Centennial Celebration Brochures, 2002 (Box 3, Folder 16)
- "An Emergency Food Worker's Guide to Food Science", 2002 (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - Safe Food at Emergency Disaster Shelters Slides and An Emergency Food Worker's Guide to Food Safety booklet, 2002; CD-3225
- Empty Milk Cartons from Cornell Dairy (Box 3, Folder 18)
- Institute of Food Science
  - Food for Thought" by David Bandler and Barbara Bubar (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - Memos, Meeting Minutes, Clippings about the Department and the Institute of Food Science, 1964-2000 (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - Newsletter of the Institute of Food Science, 1971-1974; 1979; 1994 (Box 3, Folder 21)
  - Annual Report of the Institute of Food Science, 1991-1992 (Box 3, Folder 22)
  - Advisory Council Institute of Food Science, 1993-2000 (Box 3, Folder 23)
  - Cornell Associates Program, 1999-2000 (Box 3, Folder 24)
  - "A Matter of Judgement: The Case for Food Safety in the Supermarket Deli"- Instructor's Manual (Box 3, Folder 25)
  - "A Matter of Judgement: The Case for Food Safety in the Supermarket Deli", V-7601 (Box 3)